They totally won that round!
Now I've been Bucksnapped!
I figured Sol Ream would whip out
a teleportation circle, but still,
this is my second time as a
pilfered purveyor of vending goods!
Sorry things had to turn
out this way, Boxxo.
Not to interrupt, but where am I?
Pity was in the effect
radius and got gotted.
She's been through shell and back.
On the outside, I'm just a big metal box,
but inside, I've still got a human soul!
In this new world of wonders,
I travel to and fro on the back
of my super strong partner, Lamas!
The name's Box Up! Hello there!
That means yes, by the way!
Potassium.
Digital. O?
Have you told me?
Can we feel like a father's
dream in this dream?
Oh
This dungeon stratum houses the
Netherlord's base of operations.
No way!
The Netherlord's around these parts?
Feels like I cheat-coded
my way to the final boss.
We've been trying to clear this
stratum since we made our agreement,
but we're sorely lacking
in food and supplies.
It's painfully obvious that
we desperately need your help.
Pretending we were after
pity was an elaborate ruse.
Thing is, you're the one we've
been waiting for this whole time.
Pity is just...
bycatch?
I realize it's useless to haggle with you,
so just be a sport and agree to
go exploring with us. Please?
Too bad!
Sure I can't tempt you?
Too bad.
I know the whole cursed kid
sitch is a heavy load to bear,
but I refuse to plop out a cold
can of betrayal for my pals.
Understood.
Well, I had a feeling you'd say that.
And you?
Want to team up with the fools again?
Pity can't do it.
I'm already helping Heavy
and all of the others.
I made a promise.
Even if I agree to grant you any
wish a little clan could want?
Such as reclaiming the heart
of the man you loved and lost?
All he's missing are
horns and a pitchfork!
I can't... Huh?
This is something I've
got to do on my own.
Somehow.
I'll find a way to bring him back.
So the answer's no.
Go, pity!
Her defense is OP!
And her heart is clearly
too pure for this world.
Why must I be so stubborn
about anything love-related?
Luckily for you, I'm a patient man.
I'm not going to let you out,
not until you agree to join us.
Give me the goods, Boxo!
I've got a mad craving for
that fried meat of yours!
I want some too!
They may suck, but
they're still customers.
What to do?
Just giving in sounds hella lame.
Hey, what's the big idea of replacing the
fizzy - Wait, you put her on that one!
We know you've got meats
and sweets in there!
If you insist.
Hello there.
Thanks, I knew you
wouldn't do us like that.
I wonder what I should order first.
Those prices!
Hey, that's ten times as much as usual!
Booyah!
Us humble vending machines always
charge more at destination spots,
like enemy lairs.
Please insert coins.
It's extortion or blackmail or something!
I don't wanna pay, but I'm gonna...
Uh-oh. Emergency. No toilet.
You, Pa-Octa-E.
It's pity, remember?
Thanks a bunch.
It's so soft.
you're really the best and so kind to me
it's time to rise and
shine are you kidding
me with this what's wrong did something
bad happen oh my goodness wow how lovely
it's a shame i'll have to leave one day
you're not taking this whole prisoner
thing seriously prison schmizzen it's My
duty as a vending machine to dispense joy.
I assume you both reconsidered my offer?
It's still a no.
Ever, ever.
That didn't exactly sound like a chipper.
Hello there, so I guess that
means I should take it as a no.
Come on, must we play these silly games?
You realize I'm giving you
the good cop treatment.
You won't get that from
Sulreeman, the Netherlord.
Soon you'll just be a pile
of parts and clan chowder.
I'd say you probably have one week max
Got it?
Just one week left.
Don't let it slip away.
I think he was trying to help us.
We've got to escape.
Within one week?
Yes!
Hey, Voxo, help me out?
I need another hint of food!
It's busy.
This broke is a joke.
Have some mercy, will ya?
That's just sad You want Voxo?
I'm going to destroy myself.
Must be hard to get good grub around here.
What's he doing?
It's for you.
Whoa, if we be.
You're the best magic item
with consciousness ever.
Listen up, Boxman.
I got something to say.
We really love our old buddies.
I know that sounds hard
to believe, but it's true.
We love you guys like crazy.
He's breaking our hearts.
So Shiro's a clingy drunk and
Akka's a weepy drunk. Pretty cringe.
Well, let's see what kind
of deets they let slip.
I got more to tell you.
They're these stupid five-figure generals.
Those assholes think
they're so fucking special.
Freeze, brother.
It's not that I'm complaining,
but I haven't seen the nether lord
or most of the generals in ages.
The pinky finger along
with the index finger.
Oh, and the thumb finger are missing.
I wonder what those jerks are doing.
We captured the Pinky General
in the Dark Forest Stratum.
Bet Solream's the Ring-Fingy.
If the Index and the Thumb
Generals are M .I .A.,
the Middle Fingy's around here somewhere.
In-E!
Sir!
There are a ton of monsters.
To make it worse, their
grunts are all Skellington,
so it's creepy as heck around here.
So many, I'd say there's
at least a hundred.
The Skellingtons won't even
make polite conversation.
It's so rude and majorly
hurts my feelings.
Oh, and they've got human jerks, too,
wearing these creepy coats
that aren't even a little cool.
We don't know if they're
humans or just look like it.
I kind of want one of those coats, though.
They're asleep, and they
left the door wide open.
There you are, children.
This won't do at all.
We'll discuss your drinking problem later.
Hello, Boxo.
Lady Sulream would like to speak with you.
Please accompany me.
I'm afraid pity must stay behind.
Put your backs into it.
Jeez, brutal.
Hummus must be even
stronger than I thought.
Isn't Boxo heavy?
I don't have the build for this.
I could transform into my cardboard
self, but that would be far less amusing.
You reap what you sow, kiddos.
Lady Sulream, we brought
you Boxxo as requested.
A job well done.
Now leave that thing here
and get out of my sight.
Yes, of course.
Whatever you say.
Please, stay on your guard.
Boxxo, I hear you're a sapient magic item.
I may despise humans, but I'm
fine with sentient conveniences.
Though I'll still destroy
you if you seek to oppose me.
That's weird.
Where's the captain's son?
I thought the big bummer
about the blessing of
decay was that it only
stops if she's near him.
Big Sis, where are you?
There he is.
Goodness, your hair's sopping
wet and dripping everywhere.
Such a mess.
Come let me try it.
Thanks.
You're the best, Big Sis.
Big what now?
I'm sorry for pushing you so hard earlier.
You sure you're okay?
Not a scratch on me.
Did I do a good job
pretending to be tortured?
It was perfect.
You're such a talented little actor.
Actor?
Meaning the munchkin went method
and had us totally marking out.
Now then, be careful
not to wander too far.
I won't be able to keep your
negative blessing at bay if you do.
I promise. I'll be careful.
Weird.
It's like watching a
family from an old sitcom.
I am so confused.
Hey, big sis!
Is that the talking box thing?
Yes, that's the one.
You said you wanted to
see it, and so here it is.
Go and give it a try.
Isn't it actually a real person?
And doesn't that mean we're not supposed
to let it see us stop pretending?
Don't worry yourself.
It has a rather limited vocabulary.
And there's no one here it
can speak to telepathically.
Hello there.
Wow, it really talks.
Do you think it would be okay
if I bought something from it?
Of course it would.
Buy whatever you please.
Please insert coins.
I don't have money.
Here, buy as much as you want.
It's my treat.
She is spoiling the kid rotten.
I've never seen so many
weird-looking drinks.
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe!
That expression is all kinds of wrong.
Which drink are you gonna get?
Oh, I'd be happy with anything.
Why don't you pick for me?
I've already gotten
everything I ever dreamed of.
Slee, child!
We call this shiz stranger danger!
That chick belongs on a registry.
This poor kid got curse whammy, then
woke up only to be held hostage.
It's like a Russian novel anime style.
Wait, why does he seem to respect
that walking after-school special?
Uh... Oh! Lifeline!
Since snow people are children
until they suddenly become adults,
maybe the ick factor is reduced?
I did not just think that! This is whack!
Lamas!
Save me!
Sorry, I'd love to keep playing,
but I need to take a teensy nap after
using so much stamina on teleportation.
I'm afraid I haven't fully recovered yet.
Okay, have a nice nap, but, um...
Can I have permission to buy more
stuff from Boxo while you're away?
Of course you can.
Buy whatever you want.
Just be sure to brush your
teeth if you have any sweets.
Promise!
We're alone.
I need to speak with you.
I act that way to fool her, by
exaggerating my youthfulness.
Sorry I was deceptive.
You deserve the truth.
Huh?
I know I caused my family much suffering,
and it weighs on me more
than you could know.
I'm such a burden.
The world would be much
better off without me.
But I won't waste a life they
sacrificed so much to save.
That would be a disservice to them,
and I simply couldn't bear it.
I'm masquerading as an obedient kid
to gather intel on their inner circle.
As for the curse, it truly pains
me to deceive my own family.
But my little bros are
bad at keeping secrets.
He looks like a child, but when he speaks,
it's pretty dang clear he's
older than those immature twins.
I know you have wondrous powers.
My parents told me everything
about you and your gifts.
They want you to stay here and serve them.
Refusal means destruction.
Yes.
Do you have any means of escape?
I'll gladly do anything in my
power to help you pull it off.
Think it through.
There must be a way.
The next few days, I spent my
mornings vending Pity's breakfast.
After that, I was whisked away to
Solream's pad to then some more.
After Brekkie, but before
lunch, so technically brunch,
I was wheeled to a cafeteria
with humans and beast people.
Look who it is.
I'm back.
You're early today.
What a nice surprise.
By the way, I wouldn't
say no to more food.
For today, will you stay with me?
Yes!
That makes me happy.
Is pity crushing on a
certain vending machine?
Like always, your food is delicious.
Thanks, Poxo. Say what?
Me thinks that's the first time
she's called me by my name.
Is this that suspension bridge
effect thingy from psychology?
When in imminent danger you mistake
the pounding of your heart for lust?
I swear it's just psychology, Lamas!
Psychology doesn't lie!
Please, Lamas!
I hope you're properly prepared.
Tomorrow's the big day.
Hello there!
Oh man, I almost forgot
that was even happening.
The catered meeting on the roof.
It's not fair, Akka.
Only our Big Bro, Boxo, Pitty,
and Sulream are invited to go.
Yep.
Solream's trying to pass it
off as a catered meeting,
but it's really just a
rooftop barbecue party.
All because...
Big Sis, I really, really, really
want to eat outside tomorrow.
I know it's against the rules.
Can I do it on the roof instead?
Sulream was powerless
against his S-rank cuteness.
No comment.
He even convinced her
to invite pity so she
could use her blessing of
weight to get me there.
It's the perfect chance
to escape their fortress.
If I botch this, it's probably
curtains for both of us.
It would seem the middle-fingered
general was nearby.
I heard the goons talking about it,
though we've yet to see the
general with their own eyes.
The middle thingy.
Not knowing what to expect
makes me super nervous.
Boxo, don't worry.
You'll see.
We'll be fine.
Oh, I must have been blinking.
I should be vending, not venting.
Thank you very much.
Dammit,
when I think of all the cool
stuff Boxo's about to do,
I want to ditch the netherlord.
Same for me! Team Boxxo!
Team Fried Meat and Fizzies!
Please make sure to get a nice
recording of your reunion with Lamas.
Am I the only normal one here?
Boxxo, no peeking.
Yes!
To business!
Boom!
These coin lockers preserve freshness,
so I'm using them for the big lunch.
Petitrusts in Boxo. Completely.
Looks like you're ready to roll.
Well, let's go.
No one's allowed on the roof until lunch,
so you'll be on your own until then.
Surin's orders were incredibly clean.
None shall pass!
Isn't that right, Shiro?
Yeah, not on our watch,
Aka. That's correct.
We have no choice but to
follow the orders given to us.
There's still no sign of
the Middlefinger, General.
True, and I've never seen the
Netherlord here even once.
They're not exactly being
subtle, but that's good info.
See ya.
And take care.
Goodbye.
And thank you for everything.
I mean that.
I look forward to serving you again.
I won't say goodbye.
I'm literally incapable of it.
We will meet again. Wait and see.
Here we go.
The guests of honor.
Human,
if you try anything funny,
I'll freeze you on the spot
and keep you as an ice statue.
Noted.
Beautimous.
She thinks I'm a regular old magic
item, so she's only watchdogging pity.
It's so yummy.
You should try it, big sister.
But you already drink from it.
Yeah, I guess you wouldn't want
it after it's been in my mouth.
That is the opposite of the truth.
In fact, it makes me want it more.
Mmm. Score!
That yakiniku sauce has her
slugging them back like crazy.
How come you're wiggling
like that? It's fine.
I just need a little
bathroom break. Go time!
Caffeine has a diuretic effect.
You can't chug that much
without nature calling.
I've gotta go, too.
Your name's pity, isn't it?
Don't try anything stupid while I'm gone.
It's impossible to escape.
You're trapped on a rooftop
on an isolated island.
Isn't this fun, Vixis?
Boxxo, please hurry! Yes!
Form change!
Balloon vending machine!
I'm ready.
I sure hope this works!
Octae?
It's pity!
Actually, I guess that's fine.
Activating it now.
Pity's weight blessing is in play.
She made me, herself, and her
shield light as a feather.
House, we did it!
Now for another form change!
Coin-powered vacuum!
I'll bend up some mighty wind.
Hey, Foxo, it's working!
Yes, thank you very much.
The barrier costs a lot of points.
But I've got over a mil!
So it ain't no thing.
We just gotta find an island and...
Boxo, that bin right there?
It seems to be following us!
What's the actual?
It's at least 50 meters.
Fly no further!
That bin is telepathic?
You must face punishment and for attempting
to escape the Netherlord's grasp.
As the Middlefinger General,
I will not abide this.
The Middlefingy's a shark?
You don't see that every day.
So that's why he was never at the base.
Take us higher, Balloon Brigade!
There's no escape!
Points reduced by 918.
Happy, happy!
You yellow-bellied coward!
Have you no honor within
that magic box of yours!
Voxo!
He's following us! Crossroads!
Should we try to float away or troll?
Ok, no problem.
I'm guessing you have a plan?
I do!
Form change!
Super-sized vending machine,
complete with the concrete blocks
those big mamas are bolted to.
Ready? Fire!
What the freak is going on here?
You're cucked.
Remove barrier.
Boxo!
Form change!
Nonsense!
Those things appeared as if from nowhere!
Yoo-hoo!
Super-sized Fendi-Machine attack!
Fatality.
Now all I got to do is find Pity and...
Huh?
Easier done than said.
Even if she adjusted her
weight, that was reckless.
For Octa-E.
Oh, thank goodness!
You're safe.
That must have been pretty heckin' scary.
This is about the time
Lamas would start yelling.
Legs, huh?
I guess the general was amphibious.
You okay? What's wrong?
I'm getting deja vu from when we
defeated the Netherlord's arm.
If he sees the body, he'll
know this was a boxo joint.
Here's hoping the fishies have
themselves a middle thingy feast.
Oh
I love you?
I look forward to serving you again.